Antony Budianto

Biodata



Name Antony Budianto

Gender Male

Place and Date of Birth Pontianak, August 8th, 1993

Language English (proficient), Indonesia (native)

Summary

A software engineer and open source contributor with 4+ years experience on software development, web design and development, git, writing unit and end-to-end tests, deployment and setup CI server. Actively contributing to open source and listed as one of the top 10 JavaScript GitHub developer in Indonesia by github-awards.com

Educations

September 2011 - March 2015 Binus University, Bachelor Degree, Information Systems major

Work experiences

September 2016 - present Senior Software Development Engineer

GDP Labs

September 2015 - August 2016 Software Development Engineer

GDP Labs

Develop enterprise applications using Angular JS, Angular 2.0, and Gulp

September 2014 - August 2015 Network Administrator

Binus University - Software Laboratory Center

Cloning images for software lab computers, ensure networks running well, patching,

calibration, maintenance, and develop various network-based applications

August 2013 - September 2014 Teaching Assistant

Binus University - Software Laboratory Center

Assists students in programming class, making cases, marking student assignments and

learn many hardskills and softskills

Certifications

May 2013 1st winner: HIMSISFO Competition 2013 "Infinite Creation" Web Design and Development

Competition

April 2015 5th rank: Research and Expo Competition (REOC) 2014. E-Learning Development for

Indonesian Traditional Music.

Skills

HTML, JS, CSS, React, React Native, Angular, NodeJS, Laravel, Jenkins, Docker